What about
ماذا عن
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It's not easy to use.
ليس من السهل استخدامه.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Let's try to play hard to get.
دعونا نحاول اللعب بجد للحصول عليه.
You always brush the sense of existence.
أنت دائما تنظف الإحساس بالوجود.
When she gets used to it,
عندما تعتاد على ذلك ،
hey
مهلا
And ignored her.
وتجاهلتها.
Hey, I don't believe it.
مرحبًا ، لا أصدق ذلك.
She can escape my hands.
يمكنها الهروب من يدي.
Ah, the palm of your hand.
آه كف يدك.
Your friend's boss is amazing.
رئيس صديقك رائع.
You can play hard to get.
يمكنك اللعب بجد للحصول عليها.
Have you heard of the 366 Strategy?
هل سمعت عن استراتيجية 366؟
One step back today for two steps forward tomorrow
خطوة إلى الوراء اليوم لخطوتين إلى الأمام غدًا
Don't pretend to be silly.
لا تتظاهر بأنك سخيف.
Your friend.
صديقك.
Tell your friend to pretend to be silly.
أخبر صديقك أن يتظاهر بأنه سخيف.
I made a new dish recently.
لقد صنعت طبقًا جديدًا مؤخرًا.
Give it a try.
جربها.
Don't bother.
لا تهتم.
I'm busy.
أنا مشغول.
Help me try it on.
ساعدني في تجربته
sit
يجلس
The tofu is too strong.
التوفو قوي جدًا.
Is not suitable for making desserts.
غير مناسب لعمل الحلويات.
According to Lin Zeyan's suggestion,
وفقًا لاقتراح لين زيان ،
Should be able to win the game.
يجب أن تكون قادرًا على الفوز باللعبة.
It's too spicy.
انه حار جدًا.
Without taste.
بدون طعم.
Next time it tastes so bad,
في المرة القادمة مذاقها سيء للغاية ،
The salary is deducted.
يتم خصم الراتب.
OK!
نعم!
He's too picky.
إنه صعب الإرضاء للغاية.
I will endure it for the food competition.
سوف أتحملها من أجل مسابقة الطعام.
Food competition.
مسابقة الطعام.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
Xia You Team.
فريق شيا يو.
In the first round.
في الجولة الأولى.
The second qualifying round begins now.
الجولة التأهيلية الثانية تبدأ الآن.
Go and fix the ingredients of Xia You.
اذهب وأصلح مكونات شيا يو.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Got it?
فهمتك؟
understand
تفهم
It's an honor for you to participate in the finals.
إنه لشرف لك أن تشارك في النهائيات.
The game begins.
تبدأ اللعبة.
Once again,
مرة اخرى،
To ensure the fairness of the competition,
لضمان عدالة المنافسة ،
This competition can't be used.
لا يمكن استخدام هذه المنافسة.
Ingredients other than those prepared in the restaurant
مكونات غير تلك المحضرة في المطعم
Otherwise, I will be disqualified.
خلاف ذلك ، سوف يتم استبعادني.
Cheng Mu, have you seen the candy?
تشنغ مو ، هل رأيت الحلوى؟
No.
رقم.
No sugar.
بدون سكر.
Then our dishes
ثم أطباقنا
I can't make it so delicious.
لا أستطيع أن أجعلها لذيذة للغاية.
No way
مستحيل
I must be the first.
يجب أن أكون الأول.
The game is over.
انتهت اللعبة.
Mr. Lin, these are the last two dishes.
سيد لين ، هذان هما آخر طبقين.
The first dish.
الطبق الأول.
The jade wears a thousand silk.
يلبس اليشم ألف حرير.
This jade wears thousands of silk.
هذا اليشم يلبس آلاف الحرير.
And innovative.
ومبتكرة.
Dare to match the ingredients.
يجرؤ على مطابقة المكونات.
The flavor between the ingredients is balanced and attenuated.
النكهة بين المكونات متوازنة ومضعفة.
With a hint of sweetness.
مع قليل من الحلاوة.
However
لكن
This shouldn't be the taste of sugar.
لا ينبغي أن يكون هذا طعم السكر.
The second dish.
الطبق الثاني.
Flying wings.
الأجنحة الطائرة.
The Tao is soaring.
تاو يحلق.
The taste is strong and not greasy.
الطعم قوي وليس دهني.
Soft glutinous slippery mouth
الفم الزلق الناعم اللزج
The fire is good.
النار جيدة.
It can be said that the essence of the chicken wing is in place.
يمكن القول أن جوهر جناح الدجاج في مكانه.
Your vote is...
تصويتك ...